Christmas is right around the corner,
and when I think "Christmas," I think:
Dystopian Megacity
In science fiction, Dystopian Megacitites are these...
Oversized, Financially Unstable, Deteriorating, Shit Holes
...and that's why I like them.
I can relate.
I think those traits can describe most of us.
Today, I'm going to show you how to build one in SimCity.
We need a population of ten million to be a megacity,
so this will take more than ten minutes.
Uh, yes, I know it's not a dystopian megacity yet.
Kind of embarrassed by that name.
That's better!
I am learning the game, so give me ten more minutes.
I have managed to create a dystopian mega-cozy village.
I guess I can change the video's intro, so I say that "when I think Christmas,
I think snow-covered houses."
But that would be ridiculous!
By now, you may have noticed the Eternal Winter.
City Skylines does not have seasons.
If that annoys you, I think you're being a bit of a bigot.
Remember, this game was made in Finland–
winter is all they got!
When they made the summer maps, they had to guess what summer is like.
That's why the game didn't ship with night time–
they didn't know summer had it!
But it makes sense here, because it's the future,
and this is nuclear winter.
Now, you might say, "Then why isn't there radiation everywhere?"
and that's because radiation is a hoax
made up by the radiation suit industry.
Can't be long, now.
Skyscrapers everywhere.
I have named all the police stations "Cybernetics" so we can pretend they are robot cops.
And everyone is complaining that they can't get rid of their corpses,
which makes no sense.
Outside your window, you have a perfectly fine river–what's the problem?
Anyways, currently the city has a population of 103,000!
How can we only have 103,000?!
It's gonna take days to reach ten million!
♪ [Kenji Kawai: "Ghost City, Chant II"] ♪
There we go!
149 million!
If you call it fake, you are cyber-bullying me.
But I actually succeeded.
That usually never happens in these types of videos, so...
Why do I feel so empty?
Because it looks too nice!
In science fiction, you want to think,
"Thank God I'm not living there, because I would be murdered,"
not, "Thank God I'm not living there, because I would be murdered...
...by rent!"
We need some abandoned ugly buildings.
What is the easiest way to scare off a neighbor?
That's right! Burning fossil fuels!
Every house gets their very own oil power plant.
Look at that! It's already working.
Time for me to ride my motorcycle.
♪ [Geinoh Yamashirogumi: "Kanada"] ♪
Nope. Still feeling empty.
I'm actually getting depressed, now.
But the game doesn't have a psychiatrist or a drugstore,
So, to cheer us up, I'm going to build that tower I saw on the Simpsons that one time.
Now I've forgotten all about the despair.
and the only thing I can think about is I need to build a monorail!
The game doesn't have monorails, and look at that!
I'm depressed again.
Maybe that's it, though.
They are too happy.
You can't be happy in a dystopian world!
So how do I make them... less happy?
December.
Of course.
I'm going to steal Christmas!
I shall remove every store, so no one can buy presents.
Har-har-har-har-har-har-har-har-ha–errr...
what's that?
Singing?
In this park?
[Christmas Music being sung]
They are still celebrating Christmas, even though they have no presents.
And it's located next to six coal power plants.
That can't be healthy!
But still, what happened then?
Well, in Coal Park, they say that Killian's small heart grew three sizes that day.
That empty feeling is gone.
Now that I see that people still celebrate Christmas on DECEMBER 26TH?!
What happened then?
Well, in Coal Park, they say that Killian's heart collapsed like a neuron star on crack!
You're all fucking dead!
DIE, DIE! Blood for the blood god!